const fips199CardData = [
    {
        "Front": "What are the 3 security objectives?",
        "Back": "Confidentiality, Integrity and Availability"
    },
    {
        "Front": "What are the 3 possible categorizations for an information system?",
        "Back": "Low, Moderate and High"
    },
    {
        "Front": "Describe the High Water Mark concept or HWM",
        "Back": "The HWM concept states that the security categorization of a system must be the highest value assigned for each type of information in the system. "
    },
    {
        "Front": "According to FIPS-199, when is it appropriate to use Not Applicable for a security objective when categorizing an information system.",
        "Back": "Never. In other words, there is always some level of risk to CIA when thinking about the information system."
    },
    {
        "Front": "Which security objective, as it pertains to information types, is the only one permitted to be assigned a value of Not applicable?",
        "Back": "Confidentiality"
    },
    {
        "Front": "What is a loss of Confidentiality in an information system?",
        "Back": "The unauthorized disclosure of information."
    },
    {
        "Front": "What is a loss of Integrity in an information system?",
        "Back": "The unauthorized modification or destruction of information."
    },
    {
        "Front": "What is a loss of availability in an information system?",
        "Back": "The disruption of acces to or use of information or an information system."
    },
    {
        "Front": "Describe Low Impact",
        "Back": "Low impact is expected to have limited adverse effect with degradation in mission capability, minor financial loss and minor harm to individuals."
    },
    {
        "Front": "Describe Moderate Impact.",
        "Back": "Moderate impact is expected to have serious adverse effect with significant degradation in capability, significant financial loss and significant harm to individuals. DOES NOT include loss of life or life threatening injuries."
    },
    {
        "Front": "Describe High Impact",
        "Back": "High impact is expected to have severe or catastrophic adverse effect. The organization is not able to perform one or more of its primary functions, suffers major finacial loss and loss of life or serious life threatening injuries."
    }
]

export default fips199CardData;